JASON SILVIA

CONTENT DEVELOPER & CONSULTANT

linkedin.com/in/jasonsilvia 401-451-6186 jgsilvia11@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Multi-disciplined creative professional with 10 years experience and a passion for both tech and the arts. Seeking to utilize my skills and experience in content development, consulting, technical analysis, training enablement, project management, and copywriting in the fields of marketing & advertising.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Developer & Consultant

Dec, 2020 - Present

- Founded The Creative Capital Show podcast.
 - Duties include recording, editing, social media, and podcast consulting for other businesses
- Providing design and content consulting services for businesses.
 - Provided consulting and design services to BAS PVD for "A Place With No Name" chef pop-up event series within The Dean Hotel. This project resulted in BAS PVD taking over The Dean Hotel's dining space.

Marketing Content Developer | Outco

Jul, 2022 - Nov, 2022

- Analyzed current marketing content as wall as content of competitors, created new video content.
- Advised CEO on strategies to repurpose existing training assets as marketing content.

Content Consultant | Dell Technologies

Nov, 2019 - Dec, 2020

- Analyzed, curated, and created training modules for multiple divisions.
- Advised leadership on production strategies which led to frequent updating of outdated content.
- Managed content schedules for both in-person & virtual new hire training events as well as tech-talks.

Solutions Arechitect | Dell Technologies

Jun 2017 - Nov 2019

- Designed technology solutions for sales campaigns, created materials and live demos for customers.
- Created training materials that would be utilized as core curriculum for Solutions Architects.
- Became Solutions Architect bootcamp training instructor, received highest rated training by bootcamp students.

Email Retention Marketing Specialist | Schneider Electric

Jun, 2012 - Dec, 2013

- Global admin for email creation/analysis tools Responsys and Litmus
- · Managed "Contractor's Newsletter" email campaign which went from worst to best performing email campaign of 2012.

EDUCATION

New England Institute of Technology | East Greenwich, RI

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Science - IT Networking

Full Sail University | Winter Park, FL

2004 - 2005